(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Bau!
I am Fuwawa!
And Mococo!
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
I'm ready!
行くよー！
Here we go!
Bau! Bau! Bau!
Ruffians!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime, Showtime, Anytime, Bau-bau-bau!
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy happy sisters!
Lifetime Showtime
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
Bau bau bau bau bau bau bau bau!
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA (Yay!)
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
Fuwa! Moco!
I love being tricky, doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ (Oh!)
I want to be with you (Oh!)
Lifetime, Showtime, Anytime, Bau-bau-bau!
一生涯 Sing with you
Singing with you for a lifetime
Stars wink, Moon spotlight, Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be with you
Lifetime, Showtime, Anytime, Bau-bau-bau (Yeah!)
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy happy sisters!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy days kept sealed away (Bau!)
Bouta burst, fluff & fuss, we're meant to be free
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz, we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement, dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin', but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair, just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why...
いっだって It's that day! 今日だって Today!
Always, it's that day! Today as well, today!
Lifetime! Showtime! 明日じゃない Bau Bau!
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau Bau!
一生涯 Walk with you!
A lifetime walk with you!
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter
いっだって It's that day!
Always, it's that day!
Lifetime! Showtime! 毎日 Bau Bau!
Lifetime! Showtime! Every day, Bau Bau!
Yeah, 二人は...
Yeah, the two of us...
Happy fuzzy yappy puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU! Everybody, BAU BAU!
Hallo Hallo BAU BAU! Everybody, BAU BAU!
ダメダメノンノン Don't touch the ears!
No, no! Don't touch the ears!
モフモフノンノン Don't touch the tail!
No fluffy touching! Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！バウ！
Not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
フワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！バウ！
Not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! Bau!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! BAU!
And together we're FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime, 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, I want to be with you
It's showtime, 一緒にいたいよ
Fuwa fuwa Moco moco Hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it, won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime, 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, I want to be with you
Lifetime, Showtime, Anytime, BAU BAU!
一生涯 Sing with you!
A lifetime singing with you!
Stars wink, Moon spotlight, Furr-ever glow
It's showtime, 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, I want to be with you
Lifetime, Showtime, Anytime, BAU BAU!
And together we're Happy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Let's hear you!
Say it!
FUWA! MOCO!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
Wuffians!
BAU BAU!
Welcome to our FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate our birthday with us!
始まりました！
It's started!
今日は生誕ライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to our birthday live today!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's variety show shenanigans...
Today, we have a big concert!
Can you believe it? It's already been three years!
Right, our third birthday in hololive English!
But Mococo-chan, we can't forget that really important thing, right?
Introductions!
Ah, yeah!
I'm not a chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
We're hololive English -Advent-'s twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together we're... FUWAMOCO!
BAU BAU!
And... we have an amazing birthday festival onstage here!
It's so big, Fuwawa!
I know, right?
And such a big blue stage too!
Ah, Fuwawa?
Yes?
Okay, here we go!
3, 2, 1...
BAU BAU!
It's so big and wide too!
Thank you for being such a big hit today!
But, singing and dancing today is not just going to be us, right?
No, we're also here with some very special guests too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来てるから...
Yes, because some very wonderful guests are also coming today...
楽しみにしていてくださいね！
So please look forward to it!
そして、もう一人... 謎のゲストさんも...
And, one more person... a mysterious guest as well...
誰かな〜？
I wonder who it is~?
BAU BAU!
But, a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right, something very important.
I think you know well, but...
Hashtag! Yes, the birthday hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag.
#FWMCbday26, that it is!
Please, please post your thoughts, take lots of photos, screenshots...
ぜひハッシュタグで感想呟いてください。
Please tweet your thoughts with the hashtag.
写真もね！後でポチしに行くからね！
And photos too! I'll go check them out later!
We'll check out all your thoughts after the show!
BAU BAU!
Oh!
Also!
We're going to be having a special
membership-only concert right after this,
so don't miss it, okay?
Yeah! Uh!
最後にはメン限のアンコールライブも
Lastly, there's a membership-only encore live,
ありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
so please come and watch!
Bau Bau!
Uh!
You know, it is a concert after all, right?
So should we get singing a little more, yeah?
Yeah! Yeah!
Wow! Oh!
For this next song,
I think we need a special guest for this, right?
Yeah! Uh! Okay!
Let's call her on together!
Okay!
Calli-senpai!!
Hey hey hey hey hey hey!
みなさーん！
Everyone!
Bau Bau!
Today only, I am also a dog!
Bau Bau Bau Bau Bau!
Shinigami dog!
Yeah!
Happy birthday FUWAMOCO!
Thank you for inviting me!
I'm happy to be here!
What's up Ruffians?!
But I see you have a
pretty nice shirt there, huh?
I do!
Wow!
Look at this logo!
What could it say? Check it out!
FUWAMOCO!
Yo! Yo!
Respect! Respect! Respect!
With respect! With respect!
You know, it'd be cute if we
matched, right?
Right!
Ah!
But maybe we'll just go run
and we'll let you entertain
the Ruffians for a second?
Yeah, okay!
Entertain them!
You can do it!
I got this! They won't bite!
Yeah, okay! Okay, Bau Bau!
Ruffians, welcome to
Mori Calliope's super special
splits challenge segment!
Ikuzo!
Dekinai! Dekinai!
I can't! I can't!
I can't! I'm sorry, I can't! I can't do it!
I did my best!
Daishoubu! Daishoubu!
It's okay! It's okay!
Yeah, but I can, I can still dance!
Yeah!
That's right! We're matching!
Matching! Tripling!
Tripling!
Ah!
Wow! That's a nice ring to it!
This next song is one that
FUWAMOCO, we wanted to sing with
you for such a long time!
Yeah! Yeah!
Something nostalgic, and I think
you'll be able to see why!
There's some rap in it as well!
Oh! Yeah!
But it's also very cute, right?
次に歌う曲は、Calli先輩と一緒に
The next song we're going to sing is
ずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！
a favorite song that we've always
wanted to sing with Calli-senpai!
It's both cute,
it's cool!
Yeah!
But I think, you know, it
shares an important part that...
You know,
you should be proud of what you like!
An important meaning of being proud,
being strong about what you like, yeah!
Your likes!
Uh!
Whether that be games,
anime,
idol,
figure,
or maybe even...
Vtubers!
Oh! Nice!
You missed it there!
After all, life is more fun when
you're just true to yourself, right?
Definitely! Oh! I agree!
So we're gonna sing this song for you, okay?
Okay! Let's do the title call together, okay?
Yes!
聞いてください！
Please listen!
Like! Like! Like!
Lyrics: ふわもこ
Musica: TOYA
Lyrics: FUWAMOCO
Comic, I like it!
Music, I like it!
Game, I like it!
Animation, I like it!
Figure, I like it!
Movie, I like it!
Wonder, I like it!
Hobby, I like it!
Go go go go go go go go!
Do you like it? I like it!
人生楽しんだもん勝ち、驚きさ
Whoever enjoys life wins, it's a surprise
好きなもの「好き」って言えたらそれ、スーパーノヴァ
If you can say "I like" what you like, that's a supernova
快感、中枢にそくマックス、驚きさ
Pleasure, straight to the core to the max, it's a surprise
まる裸、描き鳴らして歌う晩餐のま
Stark naked, drawing it out and singing during dinner
Fantastic! Magic! 毎日、得意でご機嫌な時間は、一生でしょう
Fantastic! Magic! Every day, the happy times I'm good at will last a lifetime
脳に、キラビやかな想像、今すぐ、Let's mix up!
Gorgeous imagination in the brain, right now, Let's mix up!
キミが部屋にいたって、リンクすればコンサート
Even if you're in your room, if we link up, it's a concert
いつだってOnly Only Only Just the number one say it!
Always Only Only Only Just the number one say it!
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば、きっと全てがカラフルで
I Like It! I Like It! If you fall in love, everything will surely be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ、光る宝物さ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust is a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた、やっと今日からヨロシクね
I Like It! I Like It! I finally met you, so nice to meet you starting today
ほら、キラキラ、夢みたい、早く抱きしめたい
Look, sparkling, like a dream, I want to hold you soon
アレもコレも欲しくて、神様に祈ってる
I want this and that, I'm praying to God
ねっ 好きでしょがない
Hey, I can't help but love it
次はなににしようかな
What should I do next?
I'll back up, worth what, talk amount why
飛ばさないコトダマ I'll never lie, yeah
Undying words of power, I'll never lie, yeah
360度パノラマ全方向大好きの陣
A 360-degree panorama, an 'I love everything' formation
何が一つでもいいから のめり込める自分のアイテム
Even just one thing is fine, find an item you can lose yourself in
Like a superstar, fireman
無敵キャンディ 他大体来世
Invincible candy, the rest in the next life
望んでる彼もきっと 現世が愛おしくなるはずなのさ
The guy you're wishing for will surely come to love this world too
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
It's not something you force, let's just enjoy life as we walk
自分に素直であれ Spotlight 僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, Spotlight, shine down on us
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ GET DOWN! Only one song for you
I'll just shout my love today too, GET DOWN! Only one song for you
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
I'm sure everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
夢の物語さ
is a dream story
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you
ずっと離さないでいてね
Please never let me go
ほら キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow
世界はまわりだす
The world starts spinning
ガチャガチャゴーゴーゴー！
Gacha gacha go go go!
パワー！
Power!
イェイイェイイェイ！
Yay yay yay!
好き好き好き勝負大！から手に入れたいこの感情
歯止めと財布と真剣勝負
I love, love, love the big match! I want this feeling
A serious battle between my restraint and my wallet
溜めらわないのがいいんでしょ？
It's best not to hesitate, right?
そう、恋をまもと実験
Exactly, love is an experiment
でもそれが僕の等身大
But that's just who I am
勝ち出す素晴らしい世界を確認
Confirming a wonderful world starting to win out
いわゆるひとつの萌え要素
It's what you'd call a 'moe' element
素直になれたなら Happy days
If I could be honest, Happy days
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If I fall in love
きっと全てがカラフルで
I'm sure everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust
光る宝物さ
is a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you
やっと今日からよろしくね
Finally, starting today, let's get along
ほら キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a dream
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hug you soon
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If I reach out my hand
きっと全てがミラクルで
I'm sure everything will be a miracle
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
ユメの物語さ
is a dream story
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you
ずっと離さないでいてね
Please never let me go
ほら キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, it's sparkling like a rainbow
世界はまわりだす
The world starts spinning
How was it, FuwaMoco?
イェイ！
Yay!
Unbelievable!
I like FuwaMoco!
We like you, Calli-chan!
Bye bye Bau Bau!
Please listen to our next song, "Jo j'aime, Jo j'aime".
街角に並ぶ映画のポスター
Movie posters lined up on street corners
もうこの街にも飽きたわ
I'm already tired of this city
明日は...
Tomorrow...
つばきの向こうにため息を返す
Returning a sigh beyond the camellias
キャンセルしないで
Please don't cancel
Mon amour pour toi
My love for you
ポケットに隠した写真
A photo hidden in my pocket
誰も知らない
A real love
本気の恋
that nobody knows
神様は気づいてる
God has already noticed
Jo j'aime ★ Jo j'aime 叶わない夢なんて
Jo j'aime ★ Jo j'aime, a dream that won't come true
見たくないわ
I don't want to see it
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is beginning to wake up
"愛してるわ"
"I love you"
クレープに描く
I draw it on a crepe
愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the non-stopping rain
Jo j'aime ★ Jo j'aime
かなわない夜に
On a night where things don't go my way
したくはないから
Because I don't want to get ready
ほんの5分でも
Even for just five minutes
会いたい
I want to see you
やんぴ、仕事も
I'll quit my job
ネコ、ドタキャンも
And cancel on my cat
あなたがいないと
If you're not here
つまらない
It's boring
ジャケットのポケットに
In the pocket of my jacket
入れたままのコインに
With a coin left inside
かけるわ 恋の行方
I'll bet the future of our love
神様が知っている
Only God knows
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love like that
したくないわ
I don't want it
あっという間に溺れてく
In the blink of an eye, I'm drowning
“今がすべて”
“Now is everything”
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before the café au lait gets cold
もいちどKISSして
Kiss me once more
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Locking up the story
どーじょー・あん・じゅ
De jour en jour
あなたの言葉ばかりを夢見ている
I'm only dreaming of your words
もう、何も
Nothing more
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて見たくないわ
I don't want to see dreams that won't come true
でもロマンス 目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up
“愛してるわ”
“I love you”
クレープに描く 愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the unending rain
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
モン・アムール、ポエトワ
Mon amour, pour toi
退屈な恋なんて
A boring love like that
したくないわ
I don't want it
あっという間に溺れてく
In the blink of an eye, I'm drowning
“今がすべて”
“Now is everything”
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before the café au lait gets cold
もいちど聞かせて
Let me hear it once more
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
La la la...
Bau Bau!
Wow! Look at the sunset!
Oh, it's setting already, Ruffians!
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime!
What did you think, Mococo?
What did you think, Ruffians?
It's a little bit more nostalgic...
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
You know, some city pop vibes too!
Oh, the choreography is cute too, right?
Oh boy!
We hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy, Ruffians!
Wow! You know, with the sunsetting now...
It's starting to feel a bit romantic almost, right?
Ah!
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call up my next guests!
Yeah!
Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! Akirose-senpai!
Bau Bau!
FUWAMOCO!
Happy Birthday!
嬉しい！ Bau Bau!
I'm so happy! Bau Bau!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
あ、自己紹介お願いします！
Ah, please introduce yourselves!
お願いします！
Please do!
はい！こんこんこんこんAZKi、AZKiでーす！
Hi! Kon-kon-kon-kon-AZKi, I'm AZKi!
はい！ホロライブ一期生、夜識はホロエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！ヤッホー！
Hi! Hololive 1st Gen's Holoelf, Aki Rosenthal, also known as Akirose! Yahoo!
Bau Bau!
AZKi先輩！アキロゼ先輩！
AZKi-senpai! Akirose-senpai!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
すごいステージ！
What an amazing stage!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
すごい嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
AZKi先輩とアキロゼ先輩の歌声がすごく大好きなので…
I love AZKi-senpai and Akirose-senpai's singing voices so much...
えー！ありがとう！嬉しい！
Aww! Thank you! We're so happy!
一緒に歌いたい曲があって…
There's a song I want to sing with you...
おー！はい！
Oh! Yes!
アキロゼ先輩とあずき先輩はとっても
Aki Rosenthal-senpai and AZKi-senpai are very...
魅力的なお姉さんたちなので
...charming older sisters, so...
あらー！
Oh my!
そうなんですかー？
Is that so?
ぜひともこの曲で
I thought I'd definitely like to
行こうかなと思いました
go with this song.
あらあら
Oh my, oh my.
ちょっとね 日も暮れてますし
You see, the sun is setting too.
確かにちょっと夕方 ちょっとロマンチックになりましたね
True, it's evening, it's become a bit romantic.
おーおー
Oh, oh.
実はちょっぴり
Actually, it might be a
セクシーかも
little bit sexy.
セクシーかも！
Maybe sexy!
セクシーな曲？
A sexy song?
教えたいことある？
Is there something you want to teach us?
お願いしたかった
I wanted to ask.
お願いしたかったですかねー
I think we wanted to ask too.
アキロゼ先輩
Aki Rosenthal-senpai,
この曲を歌う前に少しあの
um, before we sing this song,
セクシーなウォーミングアップ
could you teach us a little
教えていただけないでしょうか？
sexy warm-up?
いいですか？
Would that be okay?
セクシーウォーミングアップ！
Sexy warm-up!
OK！
OK!
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあまずセクシーな
Now, first, to make a
体を作るために
sexy body,
自分の体を
stroke your own
撫でて
body.
撫でて？
Stroke it?
撫でて
Stroke it.
頭なでなで
Stroke your head,
頭撫でて
stroke your head.
足から足から
From your legs, from your legs.
セクシー！
Sexy!
撫でる
Stroke it,
撫でてみて
try stroking it.
えー
Eh...
恥ずかしい
I'm embarrassed.
撫でて アキロゼ先輩みたいに
Stroke it, like Aki Rosenthal-senpai.
あ モコちゃん
Ah, Moco-chan.
いいよ
Nice.
OK
いいよ いいよ
Nice, nice.
いこう！
Let's go!
かわいい
Cute.
いいねー
Good.
足から足から
From your legs, from your legs.
セクシーすぎる！
Too sexy!
おーいぇー！
Oh yeah!
もう一回もう一回
One more time, one more time.
えー
Eh...
ちょっと違うかな
Is it a bit different?
あずきちゃんもなんかセクシーだけど可愛い
AZKi-chan also looked a bit sexy but cute.
ちょっと見えました
I saw it.
やっぱこうやって
I guess like this...
おー
Oh.
こう？
Like this?
おー
Oh.
セクシー！
Sexy!
いいとこ
Nice point.
あらあら
Oh my, oh my.
お尻振り振り
Shake your butt.
あ しっぽ！
Ah, tail!
しっぽ！
Tail!
しっぽ振り振り
Tail shake shake.
モコちゃんしっぽ振り振り
Moco-chan, tail shake shake.
ウォームアップ ウォームアップ ウォームアップ
Warm-up, warm-up, warm-up.
OK OK
いいんじゃない？ いいんじゃない？
Isn't that good? Isn't that good?
いいよ いいよ
Nice, nice.
ウォームアップできた！
Warm-up complete!
じゃあいい感じになりましたね
Well, that felt pretty good.
次の曲行きましょうか
Shall we go to the next song then?
おー！ うん！
Oh! Yeah!
じゃあ聴いてください
Then please listen...
DISCOTHEQUE！
...DISCOTHEQUE!
DISCOTHEQUE
Lyrics: 園田凌士
Music: 上松範康 (Elements Garden)
DISCOTHEQUE
Lyrics: Ryoji Sonoda
Music: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN', let's dance
弾ける BEAUTY LADY
Sparkling BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
ずっと 彩りたいの
I want to color it forever
潤んだ唇
Moist lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Pink, shiny nails
ガラスの向こう側に
On the other side of the glass
映る素顔 シュールだね
The reflection of my true face is surreal, isn't it?
君だけにそっと見せていたい
I want to show it only to you
心の中 瞳の奥
Inside my heart, deep in my eyes
そばにいてほしいよ
I want you to be by my side
恋のミラーボール 照らされて
Illuminated by the mirror ball of love
MY DARLIN' ねえ ヴィヴィッドな 恋しましょう
MY DARLIN', hey, let's have a vivid love
弾ける SEXY BEAUTY
Sparkling SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
ずっと 彩る MY LOVE FOR EVER
Always coloring MY LOVE FOR EVER
世界は変わる
The world changes
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
ドラマティックな 呪文で
With a dramatic spell
褪せないデジャヴ 見せつけたくて
I want to show you an unfading deja vu
カラフルな シーン ストーリー
A colorful scene, a story
心深く 刻み込む
Etched deep into my heart
小さな闇が訪れても
Even if a little darkness arrives
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the spell of love
ときめく果てない空
The fluttering, endless sky
星屑のシャワーが 降り注ぐ
A stardust shower pours down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指して行こう
So let's aim for HAPPY STATION
50/50 合わせて
50/50, together
100%以上の愛
More than 100% love
揺るぎなく ここにあると
I know it's firmly here
私を想ってる
Thinking of me
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA
LOVE FLARE, SHE'LL BE DOOMED
COMES UP TO THE BLAST BOOM
君に ありのまま
To you, just as I am
好きでいて欲しいと
I want you to keep liking me
願わば
If I may wish
素敵なら
If it's wonderful
Yeah!
MY DARLING もっと 一緒に踊りましょう
MY DARLING, let's dance together more
BITTERSWEET NIGHT 素敵な
BITTERSWEET NIGHT, a wonderful...
ナビ添える デコレーション
...decoration that guides us
二人のハート 合わさって
Our two hearts come together
重なり合わせて
And overlap each other
MY DARLING ねぇ ダイアモンドな恋しましょう
MY DARLING, hey, let's have a diamond-like love
はじける Sexy Beauty
Popping Sexy Beauty
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る My Love ほら
Gently coloring my love, look
世界は変わる
The world changes
Chu-lu chu-lu chu-lu pa-ya-pa
Kiss me 愛してる
燃え尽きるわ この恋 多分
This love will probably burn out
どんな結末が来ようとも
No matter what end comes
覚悟してる
I'm prepared
余裕なんて ほとんどない
I have almost no leeway
必死にしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on
あなたの瞳 優しく抱き寄せる腕
Your eyes, your arms gently pulling me close
すべてが すべてが 初めてなの
Everything, everything is a first for me
I'm falling in love with you
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let go
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just stay natural
この不安も 拭い取ってね
Wipe away this anxiety too, okay?
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ...
Hey, hey, hey...
Touch me その指先
Touch me with those fingertips
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me with that gaze
この私を 包み込んで
Envelop me
Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you
蘇るわ 昨日のこと
Yesterday's memories come back
あんなに心が震えたの 初めてだもん
Because it was the first time my heart trembled like that
寂しすぎて 時々怖い
It's so lonely it's sometimes scary
二人でいれない この時が
These moments when we can't be together
雨の朝 温かな部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room
大人の振りから 本物の大人になりそう
From acting like an adult, I might become a real one
Kiss me 危険なほど
Kiss me, to a dangerous extent
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss
この願いを 全部叶えて
Grant all of these wishes
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ...
Hey, hey, hey...
Knock me その口癖で
Knock me with those pet phrases
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window
この私を 安心させて
Give me peace of mind
Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you
Kiss me いけないほど
Kiss me, to a forbidden degree
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss
こんな願いを全部かなえて ねえ
Fulfill all these wishes for me, hey
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Knock me その魂で
Knock me with that soul of yours
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, bang on the window
この私を安心させて Please
Make me feel at ease, please
Please Please Please Please Please Please Please Please
愛してる
I love you
Waffie! Are you ready?
トライアングル・ドリーマー / Lyrics, Music: 村カワ基成
Triangle Dreamer / Lyrics, Music: Motonari Murakawa
Let's go!
Please enjoy, Triangle Dreamer!
Day by day 日々に募るの 乙女心
Day by day, a maiden's feelings grow stronger
同じクラスのナナメ前の あたらしい人
The new person sitting diagonally in front of me in class
かっこよくはない だけど優しい いつも頼れる彼
He's not cool, but he's kind, and I can always rely on him
放課後 内緒の帰り道 何だって話せる親友の女の子
On the secret way home after school, with my best girl friend
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて 女子力MAXです
She's athletic, smart, and her femininity is at MAX
どこにでもある よくある事 急に彼女が
It's a common story, when suddenly she says...
「あのね 実は私 好きな人がいるの」
"Um, actually, there's someone I like."
て ちょっとマジで！？
Wait, are you serious!?
三角形の 恋はきまぐれ
A love triangle is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A flag like in a cliché manga
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて 残念すぎます
I never thought I'd be the one to set it off, how unfortunate
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a love triangle is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's not a category where you can just say 'just kidding'
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship, swaying back and forth
なんか青春しちゃいます
I'm having a youth moment
わたし 困っちゃいます
I'm in a bind
♪トライアングル・ドリーマー
♪ Triangle Dreamer
私 悩んじゃいます
I'm so troubled
あわわ、すごい、やばい！
Awa, that's so crazy!
好きだよ、好きだけど、ってそういう意味じゃなくって、
I love you, I do, but not in that way, I mean...
だって、女の子同士だし...
...it's because we're both girls...
ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
私、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプ・ミー！
Help me!
なんか変だ 愛に国境も
Something's strange, love has no borders...
年も性別も関係ない
...nor does age or gender matter
けど、けど、けど...
But, but, but...
三角形 三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, triangle love is whimsical
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance collapses
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
Even though I dreamed of a normal love...
ノーマル設定の私じゃ
...for the "normal" setting me...
ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
...it's just a bit too much of an unbeatable game
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
Just kidding, just kidding won't suffice for this category
彼女のこと 好きになれたらな
If I could just fall in love with her...
なんて妄想しちゃいます
...that's the kind of delusion I'm having
私 どうかしてます
Something's wrong with me
行くよー！
Here we go!
Wow! Awesome!
Oh my god, it's so much fun! Wow!
Happy birthday FuwaMoco!
You look not looking very silly at all, Mococo!
You don't look silly at all, Mococo!
Miko-senpai! Wow! Hi!
I think I need to get out of here!
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
Thank you Ruffians!
That was so much fun!
Yeah, you know, I got a bit dizzy though...
...with the bubble and then changing so quickly!
Nice and fast!
Yeah, you know, just the bubble there was a little bit silly...
...but did we surprise you?
And we got to see you as well, even more close-up than usual.
Yeah! Wow, those last two songs we sang was...
...Kiss Me, I Stayed Together with Ah-kun...
...and Triangle Dreamer!
With Miko-senpai, Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
What'd you think, Ruffians?
Now Kiss Me, I Stayed Together, it's a song that...
...I've always wanted to sing together with Ah-kun!
Yeah, it's a little bit more sexy... a bit sexy song, huh? Yeah.
And Triangle Dreamer!
Yeah! The bestest idol song!
Yeah, so the Yuri development was too cute...
Ruffians... are you still alive?
Are you alive?
Yeah! All senpai were so cute in love.
Yeah, and then crowd surfing on the bubble!
Whoa!
It was a first... a lot of firsts this year, right?
Yeah! Well, we have a tiny... tiny announcement.
Huh?
You know, it's FuwaMoco, it's our birthday, right?
Right, our birthday!
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you!
Okay!
Okay! ドドーン！バウバウ！
Okay! Do-do-n! Bau bau!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays...
...with our FUWAMOCO 2026 Birthday Merch!
フワモコの生誕グッズ紹介、始まるよー！
FuwaMoco's Birthday Merch introduction starts now!
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols with the...
...Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands!
Drawn by our Mama, Icomochi-mama!
They're rather big compared to regular acrylic stands...
...so we think they'd be a great addition to your collection!
大きめサイズの、可愛いアイドルのフワモコアクリルスタンド！
Large-sized, cute idol FuwaMoco acrylic stands!
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel...
...and Hoeh!? Devil rubber figurines!
Small palm-sized figurines, perfect for displaying on your desk!
ハロウィン衣装のフワモコが、手のひらサイズのラバーマスコットになったよ！
FuwaMoco in Halloween costumes have become palm-sized rubber mascots!
This one is big!
We finally have FuwaMoco plushies in our out-and-about casual outfits!
But this time, we also speak in your houses!
It's the Yappy Puppy FuwaMoco Sounds Plushies!
We'll be the same size as our Friends with U plushies, so you can display them together!
おしゃべりパッピーMOCOCOぬいぐるみのふわもこだよ！
I'm the Talking Puppy MOCOCO Plushie, Fuwamoco!
ぎゅっとすると色々と喋るよ！
If you squeeze me, I'll say all kinds of things!
どんなボイスが出るかお楽しみに！
Look forward to hearing what voices I have!
We have the Fuwawa and Mococo to GO☆ Finger Puppets!
They both come with one extra Ruffians kigurumi costume
you can dress up in and bring around with you everywhere!
FUWAWAとMOCOCOの指パペット！
FUWAWA and MOCOCO Finger Puppets!
どこでも一緒に連れていけるサイズで、
着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
They're a size you can take anywhere,
and they come with a Ruffians costume!
Finally, we have two different ASMR voice packs:
"Back from a Fluffy Date♡" from Fuwawa...
...and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo.
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語、
両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in
both English and Japanese!
They make our hearts beat so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
The merch is separated into two sets:
Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch.
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses,
including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはふわわセットと
もここセットに分かれています！
The merch is divided into
the Fuwawa set and Mococo set!
セットごとにチェキ風カードと
特典ボイスが付きます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card
and a bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica
signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは、直筆サイン入りだよ！
The limited-edition set includes a hand-written signature!
We put lots of love into each and every signature,
so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛情を込めて、サイン書きますね！
I'll write the signatures with lots of love!
Please check out the hololive Official Online Shop and
look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひ、ホロライブ公式ショップを
チェックしてください！
Please be sure to check out the
hololive Official Shop!
Bau bau!
What did you think, Ruffians?
Of our birthday merch! Pretty cute, huh?
Yeah!
The reservations will be going on sale right
after the birthday live here ends, so don't forget, okay?
生誕のグッズの予約は、この後開始しますので、
Pre-orders for the birthday merch will start after this,
お忘れなくチェックしてください！
so please don't forget to check it out!
You can find the link below or on the side here!
Don't forget, okay? Bau bau!
We put a lot of love into it, and Icomochi-mama too!
Time to go, go, go! Go buy it!
Well, we performed
another special collab song with our dear senpai!
But there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
まだ会ってない、謎のゲストが一人いるんだよ！
There's one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Well, should we give the Ruffians a hint?
Ruffians, who could it be?
Hokuro P?
YAGOO-san?
Ah, YAGOO-san! That's a good guess maybe, but...
Well, you should get ready, because...
You know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero,
but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Mococo-chan, you're not going to be rude to our next guest
or anything, right? Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Well, let's get them out here then!
Who could it be? Okay, se-no... douzo!
Who could it be? Okay, one, two... come on out!
わわわわ！きたしんや！きたしんや！
Wa wa wa wa! I've arrived-shin! I've arrived-shin!
きたしんや！
I've arrived-shin!
ポポンちゅー！
Popon-chu!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！わわわわー！
I'm Kuro-chan! Wa wa wa wa!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ！ふわわだよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
ふわわじゃないよ！もここだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
二人合わせて、ふわもこです！
Together, we are FuwaMoco!
バウバウ！よろしくお願いします！
Bau bau! Nice to meet you!
ふわもこのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to FuwaMoco's
Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ！ふわもこ！
Happy Birthday-shin! FuwaMoco!
いいしんねー！
It's great-shin!
ちょっとね、視聴者のラフィアンズは
たくさんいると思いますけど、
I'm sure there are many Ruffians watching,
クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
自分でんの？それ？ introduction!
I have to do it myself? Okay, introduction!
わかったしんよ。だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね。
Got it-shin. People from overseas are watching too, right?
海外の人もわかる自己紹介しますからね。
I'll do a self-introduction that overseas people can understand.
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, chu, chu, chu, chu, Tulip!
え、困らないで。クロちゃんはチューリップ？
Wait, don't look puzzled. Kuro-chan is a tulip?
チューリップ？ No no no!
Tulip? No no no!
え、ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから。
Maybe they don't understand yet.
えーとに、安田大サーカスというトリオを組んでる芸人さんで、
Well, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus,
あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってまして、
and I'm also the producer for Mameshiba no Taigun,
作詞とかもしています、クロちゃんです！バウバウ！
and I write lyrics too. I'm Kuro-chan! Bau bau!
じゃあ今度は英語でお願いします！ In English!
Now do it in English! In English!
僕が？自分で？
Me? By myself?
え、そんなこと急に言われたら… It's Shine! Flower!
If you ask me so suddenly... It's Shine! Flower!
No no no!
言い訳はなし！
No excuses!
聞いてる？人の話！
Are you listening? To what I'm saying!
頑張って！
Good luck!
えっと、なんだろう... えっと...
Uh, what should I say... Uh...
Famous Comedian!
Idol Producer!
やってるしんよ！
He's actually doing it!
できるしんよ！
He can do it!
クロちゃんテレビでよく見てるけど...
We often see Kuro-chan on TV, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットのペロちゃんと、えっと、ちょっと似てるところがたくさんあるね！
There are a lot of similarities to FuwaMoco's pet, Pero-chan!
ちょっと後ろの飾り見てください！見えますか？
Please look at the decorations behind us! Can you see them?
そっくりでペロです！ペロ！
He's a spitting image of Pero! Pero!
ちょっと待って！球体というか、丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait a minute! Isn't it just that he's spherical, or round, that's similar?
そうじゃない！
That's not it!
本当？
Really?
えっとクロちゃんと似てるところは、嘘つきで、女の子好きで、やらしい... うん！
The similarities to Kuro-chan are: a liar, a lady-killer, and lecherous... yep!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで！クロちゃんはそれで大丈夫なの？言われて...
So, don't be fooled by appearances! Is it okay for Kuro-chan to be told that?
いや、ひどい！悲しくなってきた！え〜ん、え〜ん、え〜ん！
No, that's mean! I'm getting sad! Waaah, waaah, waaah!
エンポコエンフン！
En-po-ko-en-fu!
全然人のギャグを聞かないよね、君たちは！
You guys really don't listen to other people's gags!
できればクロちゃんはペロの友達になってくれませんか？
If possible, won't you become Pero's friend, Kuro-chan?
フワモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達になるの？
Not FuwaMoco's friend, but Pero's friend?
フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから！
Because FuwaMoco doesn't want to be friends with Kuro-chan!
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that strange?
いやいや、気持ち悪いから！
No, no, because it's gross!
気持ち悪くない！マニアには受ける！
It's not gross! Enthusiasts will love it!
違う！フワモコ気持ち悪いやっぱり！
No! FuwaMoco thinks it's gross after all!
でもモコちゃん、ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼です！
But Mococo-chan, that's a bit too much, it's rude!
いや、もしもしペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら、フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんに可愛く頼んだほうがいいんじゃない？
Well, if you want me to get along with Pero, shouldn't FuwaMoco-chan ask Kuro-chan cutely?
はぁ？ NO！
Hah? NO!
えっ、NO？
Eh, NO?
NO！
NO!
しっかりとした否定！
A firm rejection!
NO！
NO!
ま、けどペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいと思ってるよ！
Well, but Pero is cute, so I think it's okay for us to get along!
あ、嬉しい嬉しい嬉しい！
Oh, happy happy happy!
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな！
He's not cute, but I'd be happy if you guys got along!
感情が、感情がいろいろありすぎるのよ、本当に！
There are just too many, too many different emotions, really!
まあまあ！クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？ねっ！
Anyway! Kuro-chan, you're a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
そう、もともとアイドルなろうと思ったのに、騙されて芸人にさせられたから、アイドルは本当に夢、ドリーム！
Yes, I originally intended to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian, so being an idol is truly my dream, DREAM!
なんか悲しいな、かわいそう！
That's kind of sad, poor guy!
でもドリームって大事ですからね！
But dreams are important!
大事！
Important!
さ、で、まあクロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、もうせっかく一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
So, well, since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol, won't you please sing with us since you're here?
いいしんや、いいしんや！ オッケーだししんや！
Good, good! It's okay!
え、なに？ うん、この曲と踊らなきゃね！
Eh, what? Yeah, we have to dance to this song!
えっ、何？ この曲と踊るのね？
Eh, what? Dance to this song?
あの、ハードル上げないで！
Um, don't raise the bar!
大丈夫ですよ、ね？
It'll be fine, right?
アイドルのプロデュースもやってるし！
Since you're also an idol producer!
そうそう！
True, true!
実力見せてよ！
Show us your skills!
見せて！
Show us!
オッケーだししんや、行くしんや、行くしんや！
Okay, let's go, let's go!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a very cute song together!
え、何の曲？ 楽しみ！
Eh, what song? I'm excited!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！
Then, let's do the title call together!
ね！
Yeah!
うん！
Yep!
せーの！ ちゅ、多様性。
One, two! Chu, Tayousei.
ちゅ、多様性やるの？
We're doing Chu, Tayousei?
我愛你 酔いが醒めない
I love you, I can't sober up
Oh, I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, this love won't fade
お星様様のなれ果て 挿して
Stick in the ruins of the stars
無問題 破裂してみて
No problem, try bursting
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対 お手お座りでハイ❤報酬
Strong opposition, give me your hand, sit, here's your ❤ reward
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat is tingling
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping
鼓動で孤独 消してみてよ
Try to erase my loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も毒殺して
Poison both affection and love
僕を独占して
Monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよ
Let's keep kissing until we become addicted
そして Get get get on, Get get get on, Get on chu!
And get get get on, get get get on, get on chu!
熱く とろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
Emotions overflowing so hot they're melting...
たまらないでしょ
...it's unbearable, right?
Get get get on, Get get get on, Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題 Get Get Get on chu!
I love you, no problem, get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pon, chi, kan, the game is always...
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
...ridiculous, if you ask me...
チンプンカンプンだね 最後はロンでしょ？
...it's all gibberish, the end is a win (ron), right?
もう何回 やられればいい？
How many more times should I be beaten?
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, I can't forget
終わんない トキメキ 偏愛 予習
Never-ending excitement, practicing my biased love
喉の奥が チクンチクン
The back of my throat is tingling
僕は ドクンドクン
My heart is thumping
心臓ごと 引きずり出してみせてよってよ
Show me how you drag out my heart and all
気持ちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, even if it's a bother
やっぱ 照れくさいけど
I'm still shy, though
死ぬまで 忘れられない チューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget
いかれた街は ゾンビで溢れる
The crazy town is overflowing with zombies
愛は僕に 恋して
Love, please fall for me
ときめく胸に つながるロープを 引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to your throbbing chest
Bet bet bet on chu!
本気で 狂えるくらいの 愛おしさが
A loveliness that could drive you truly mad
美しいでしょ
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on chu!
せーの
One, two!
ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Pon, Chii, Kan, it never ends
Get Get Get on chu!
我爱你 無問題
Wǒ ài nǐ, no problem
Get Get Get on chu!
わー！やったー！うまくいったしんよー！
Wow! We did it! It went great-shin!
ありがとう！よかった！頑張ったね、クロちゃん！楽しかった！ありがとう！
Thank you! That was great! You did your best, Kuro-chan! That was fun! Thank you!
よかったー！サンキュー！
I'm so glad! Thank you!
え、ちょっとね、さよならする前に...
Um, before we say goodbye...
ほう、何？
Oh, what is it?
えっと、1個お願いしてもいいですか？
Could we ask you for one favor?
1個だけだしんや。
Just one favor-shin, then.
あっ、1個だけじゃあ...
Ah, just one then...
えっと、フワモコは魔界の番犬で、「バウバウ」ってよく言ってるんですけど...
Well, FuwaMoco are the Demon Guard Dogs, and we often say "BAU BAU"...
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、フワモコのように、可愛い「バウバウ」をしてもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, could you face the camera and do a cute "BAU BAU" just like us?
えー、できるかしん...
Eh, I wonder if I can-shin...
いくしんよ！
Here I go-shin!
バウバウ！
BAU BAU!
バウ！それがベスト！
BAU! That's the best!
え、もう1回、もっとやって！
Eh, one more time, do it more!
バウバウ！
BAU BAU!
可愛いかな？実はもう1個やりたいことがあるんですけど。
Was that cute? Actually, there's one more thing we'd like to do.
何？
What is it?
そう、さっきもやりましたけど、フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって。
Well, we did it earlier, but FuwaMoco has a signature self-introduction.
できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
If possible, we'd like to do it together with the three of us!
あ、あれ可愛かったからやりたいだしん！
Oh, that was so cute, I want to do it-shin!
じゃあ、いきますよ。
Alright, here we go.
チワワじゃないよ、フワだよ！
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwa!
ワワワワワ！フワじゃないよ、クロちゃんだよ！
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa! I'm not Fuwa, I'm Kuro-chan!
クロちゃんじゃないよ、モコだよ！
I'm not Kuro-chan, I'm Moco!
3人合わせて...
All three together...
バウバウ！
BAU BAU!
何ですか？怒んないで。
What's wrong? Don't be mad.
どうしたの？
What happened?
ちょっとちょっと、クロちゃん！
Hey, hey, Kuro-chan!
出てこないから。何なの、それ。
You didn't come out right. What was that?
もう嘘とかつくよね。おい！
You're lying to us again. Hey!
つかないと、
If you don't stop,
モコがパンチしちゃう！
Moco will punch you!
痛い！
Ouch!
救急車1台！
Get an ambulance!
いらないよ。もう嘘とか何なの、それ。バウバウ！
We don't need one. Seriously, what's with the lies? BAU BAU!
何でバウバウ怒るの、ちょっと。
Why are you BAU BAU-ing so angrily?
落ち着いて、落ち着いて。大丈夫、モコちゃん、大丈夫。
Calm down, calm down. It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay.
じゃあ、クロちゃんはこれからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Well, Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
まーしよー！
Let's do it-shin!
バウバウ！じゃあモコちゃん、
BAU BAU! Now Moco-chan,
最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね。
let's high-five Kuro-chan and say our goodbyes.
オッケー。
Okay.
仲直り、仲直り。仲直り？
Let's make up. Make up?
オッケーしんよ。ハイタッチ、ハイタッチ。ほらほらほら...
Okay-shin! High-five, high-five. Come on, come on...
やってみて、やってみて。ほら、やってやって。ほら、仲直り、仲直り。
Go ahead, try it. Come on, do it. Look, we're making up.
ですわ！
TAKE THAT!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ひどくない、ちょっと！何なの！
Isn't that cruel! What's wrong with you!
けど、フワモコちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございます！
But FuwaMoco-chan, a very happy birthday to you both!
ありがとう！おめでとうしんよ！
Thank you! Happy birthday-shin!
キュンからのバッキュン！おめでとう、ハート！
Kyun and then Bakkyun! Congrats, heart!
バウバウ！レッツゴー！
BAU BAU! Let's go!
Fireworks!
たーまやー！ かーぎやー！
Tamaya! Kagiya!
バウバウ！
BAU BAU!
Wow! That was so high-quality!
The visuals got really crazy, though, I'm not too sure what happened.
さっきの色々すごすぎて、分からなくなってきたかも。
Everything that just happened was so intense, I might be losing it.
But we still have one more thing! One more very exciting thing to show you!
まだまだお楽しみがあるよ！
There's still more fun to be had!
Maybe Ruffians can guess what it is?
何かな、何かな？
I wonder what it is?
Well, FuwaMoco, and our first anniversary...
We were able to release our very, very first original song...
...POINT TO B-O-U-L-D-E-R!
And then for our second anniversary, we were able to release "Lifetime Showtime"...
...our original song that's been with us along this journey. A very special song.
And, you know, for FUWAMOCO, singing and dancing is something that means so much to us.
Yeah, music! And, Ruffians...
...might have heard that you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Yeah! Yeah! What do you think? Yeah!
Well, our announcement is... Drumroll!
Okay, drumroll! Yes!
TA-DAN! A NEW ORIGINAL SONG!
Yeah! 二曲目の新オリ曲！
Yeah! Our second original song!
And, this song is extra special! It's written by none other than the legendary...
...rock-idol song composer, Matsukuma Kenta-san! Who works with many famous idol groups that we love.
Also written music for the idol group that Kuro-chan produces, MAMESHIBA NO GUNSHIN-san! Yeah!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay? So get ready.
Ruffians, with this song, we'd like to express our rawest feelings as Demon Dogs.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
Lyrics: 海野水玉 Music: 松隈ケンタ
Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
Lyrics: Unno Mizutama Music: Matsukuma Kenta
Arrangement: SCRAMBLES
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"Partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
Passing through the side of the neon lights
バブルガムが
When the bubblegum
はじけたら let's go
pops, let's go
最低な夜を潜って
Diving through the lowest of nights
僕らは群れをなす
We form a pack
「あの頃よりもマシだね」
"It's better than back then,"
my way
「不完全なんです」
"I'm incomplete"
首輪を
Wearing
つけた
a collar
良い子なんかじゃ
I'm done with being
もうイヤ
a good kid
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
噛みついていけ
go on and bite
この街は
This city
檻のようで
is like a cage
気分はどうだい
How are you feeling?
泣いているのかい
Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
I want to keep screaming
stray dogs
彼方へと
Towards the distance
飛ぶ鳥を
Are you just looking up
見上げるだけかい
at the flying birds?
それでいいのかい
Is that okay with you?
震えるなら
If you're trembling,
ほら青く
look, turn blue
「説教なんかいらない」
"I don't need any lectures"
スプレー
Shaking
缶振って
a spray can
イタズラ書きで
Decorating the runway
彩る
with
runway
graffiti
愛情なんか
Affection is like
coin toss
a coin toss
誰に
Who will you
bet するのか
bet on?
不確定要素
Nothing but
ばかりね
uncertain elements,
lonely
二人で
We decided
ひとつと決めた
to be two in one
あの目を
I won't forget
忘れない
those eyes
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
満天の空
the starry sky
あの星が
That star is
ひどく不快で
terribly unpleasant
勝利はどうだい
How is the victory?
味がするのかい
Does it have a taste?
鎖を噛んで
Biting the chains
唸っていたいんだ
I want to keep growling
stray dogs
僕ら
Even the universe,
宇宙さえも
we'll shoot
打ち落として
it down
見下ろす
Looking down
奈落
at the abyss
孤独を
We shared
分け合い
and ate
食べた
loneliness
あの日を
I won't forget
忘れない
that day
嗚呼
Ah
夜を睨んだ stray dogs
Stray dogs glaring at the night
そうだ
That's right,
怪物とは世界のほうさ
the world itself is the monster
抜け出せるのかい
Can you get out?
足は動くかい
Are your feet moving?
走るなら
If you're going
今
to run, it's now
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
stray dogs
僕ら
we...
この街を
Run through
駆けて行け
this city
地獄の果てに
At the end of hell
何が見えるかい
What can you see?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
I want to keep screaming
stray dogs
僕ら
we...
この街は
This city
檻のようで
is like a cage
君ならどうだい
How about you?
共に駆けるかい？
Will you run with us?
夜明けが
The dawn
合図だ
is the signal
行こう
Let's go
side by side
Lyrics: Kris Roche
Music: Aiobahn, 81, Kris Roche
Arrangement: Aiobahn, 81
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow
if you stay by my side
Dancing harmonics feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been rough times when nobody wanted us,
we kept going and we kept dreaming!
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore!
Still we're here together, we have smiles to protect!
Come on, let's go!
Dancing harmonics feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya, nya...
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore, everyone!
That was "side by side"!
We're really happy to perform "side by side" for the first time live today!
初披露できてとっても嬉しいです！
I'm so happy we could perform it for the first time!
"side by side" is a song made by Aiobahn-san, but also between FuwaMoco and us!
We know it's a song that you love a lot, but we also do because it's very special to us...
...since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about... NEKOPARA!
And with this song, our dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
そう！この曲でFUWAMOCOの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
Yes! With this song, FuwaMoco's dream of singing a theme song for a bishojo game has come true!
And thank you so much for joining us for our special day again this year!
It's been a dream, everyone!
And you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here and do all the amazing things that we do. So thank you!
This next song is our last song.
Aw... but like all of them, it's a very special one.
You know, FUWAMOCO as demon guards,
we're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that.
Protect your smile!
Yeah!
Do our best idol...
...and just as our fluffy and fuzzy souls too. Yeah.
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of demon dog years,
all while remembering that, you know, every day isn't given.
Yeah.
We don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down,
we hope that you'll remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We'll cheer you on Ruffians!
Yeah!
So, please listen closely to the lyrics...
...of our last song for today.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling,
ずっと...
forever...
lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things are rough, and know that we'll be here!
This last song is for you!
Wishful Garnet!
過去を振り返ると
Looking back at the past,
思い出す ガーネットの空
I remember the garnet sky.
溢れてく光
The overflowing light.
この瞳に
In these eyes...
映し出された あの日は
...that day was reflected...
美しく
...beautifully.
揺れる
Swaying.
What do you think?
赤く滲んだ空に
In the sky stained red.
願いました
I made a wish,
どうかこの願い
please, let this wish...
届けてください
...reach you.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も
and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we're far apart,
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward.
あなたを 縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
woah
もう負けないで
Never give up
進むこと
and keep moving forward.
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I'll always be by your side.
落ち込んだり
Even when you're feeling down
自信を無くした時だって
or lose your confidence.
目の前にいてくれる
You are right there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度も
Your smile has, many times,
救われた
saved me.
だから
That's why.
So I love you
挫けそうになったら
If you're about to give up,
手を伸ばして
reach out your hand.
まだ知らない
To an unknown...
明日
...tomorrow.
一緒に見つけよう
Let's find it together.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も
and the day after too,
あなたを照らしていたい
I want to keep shining on you.
泣きそうになった時は
When you're about to cry,
こっち向いてほしい
I want you to look this way.
世界で ひとりのぼっち
In this world, all alone...
そんな風に思わないで
...don't think like that.
愛して
The people who...
くれる人はきっと
...love you will surely...
いつもあなたを想ってる
...always be thinking of you.
ooh... yeah...
Wishful Garnet
lala...
願いました
I made a wish,
どうかこの願い
please, let this wish...
届けてください
...reach you.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も
and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we're far apart,
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward.
あなたを 縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
woah
もう負けないで
Never give up
進むこと
and keep moving forward.
輝く空へ
To the shining sky.
明日も
Tomorrow,
明後日も
and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are separated
前を向けますように
I hope you can keep looking forward
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you
わたしが壊してあげる
I'll break them for you
wow wow...
もう負けないで進むこと
Never give up and keep moving forward
いつでもそばに
Always by your side
あなたのそばに
Right by your side
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I'm always here with you
La la la la...
Oh yeah, yeah yeah yeah...
BAU BAU!
Thank you so much for viewing!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
BAU BAU!
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メンバー限定アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
Waiting for you at the member-only encore live!